Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Marvin Leath papers
Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
14
Leath, Marvin, 1931 - 2000
431 document boxes and 36 oversize boxes.
The Marvin Leath papers are comprised of material from the Congressional career of Marvin Leath, 1980-1991. Records include administrative files, agencies and departmental files, correspondence, legislation, A/V materials, and awards.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
James Marvin Leath (1931-2000) was born in Henderson, Texas, on May 6, 1931. After attending Kilgore Junior College, Leath attended the University of Texas at Austin where he played lineman as a member of the 1953 winning Cotton Bowl team. He went on to receive his B.B.A. in 1954. Leath's road to Congress went through a stint in the U.S. Army (1954-1956), a football and track coaching position at his alma mater, Henderson High School (1957-1959), and business careers as a salesman, banker, and executive in the banking and manufacturing industries. From 1972-1974, he worked as a special assistant to W.R. Poage, U.S. Representative for Texas’s 11th District. When Poage retired in 1979, Leath ran for Poage's seat and won.
Leath served as the U.S. Representative for Texas’s 11th Congressional District from 1979-1990 as a Democrat. A conservative Southern or “Boll Weevil” Democrat, Leath remained ideologically aligned with his Republican colleagues on fiscal matters throughout his tenure in the House. He vigorously supported free market policies, spending cuts, and tirelessly worked for a balanced budget amendment to the Constitution. Moreover, Leath fervently pursued a policy of peace through strength and supported increased defense spending as well as nuclear armament. While in Congress, he served on the Armed Services Committee and the Public Works and Transportation Committee. Additionally, he chaired the House Subcommittee on Foreign Affairs and Defense of the Budget Committee.
Throughout his twelve-year Congressional career, Leath remained particularly devoted to the interests of the U.S. Army installation Fort Hood --one of the largest worldwide Army bases-- in his home district in Texas. He lobbied to keep the TCATA program at Fort Hood instead of moving it to Fort Ord in California. Leath also made an unsuccessful, but highly touted, bid for the chairmanship of the House Armed Services Committee. Other major legislative priorities included agriculture, banking and finance, veterans affairs, oil, and social security reform. He did not seek re-election to the 11th District seat in 1990.
After his retirement in 1991, Leath formed Marvin Leath Associates, a government consulting agency focused on the defense industry, based in Arlington, Virginia. In 1954, he married Alta Ruth Neill. Marvin and Alta have one son, Thomas, and separated in 1991. He remarried and later separated from a second wife, Penny. Leath also had a lifelong love of playing country music that started during his UT Austin days. He died December 8, 2000, at the age of 69 in Arlington Hospital. The visitors center at Fort Hood is named in his honor.
Scope and Content
This collection holds materials from Leath’s congressional career in the U.S. House of Representatives, the bulk of which cover the years 1979-1991. The administrative series consists of office paperwork and contact information for personal administrative letters, non-governmental groups, scheduling, constituent requests, and office internship and financial records from 1975-1990. Leath’s fiscal conservatism makes the finances subseries an interesting and relevant one. In agencies, government departments who wrote Leath between 1978-1980 are represented. Moreover, correspondence covers Leath’s letters to and from constituents and other members of Congress on a wide variety of issues from 1979-1990.
The fourth series includes Leath’s contact with various departments, boards, and commissions in his district and Washington, D.C. Leath’s governing priorities and the composition of his district shine through the prominent materials in the departments subseries: communication with the Departments of Agriculture, Defense, and Treasury. One fascinating piece of the small Executive Branch series is personal correspondence between Leath and Ronald Reagan on Reagan’s economic plans. Other materials in that series are information on White House tours and press releases spanning the years 1979-1987. The Legislative series is the sixth and largest series of the collection. It has three subseries and covers legislative materials by topic, Leath-authored bills, and important bills Leath kept from the 96th-101st Congresses. In the Press series, his famed and blunt newsletters, constituent comments on the newsletters, and their drafts are held. Also, the Press series contains Leath’s press releases, mailings, speeches, and radio transcripts. The radio tapes connected to the transcripts are in the Audio-Visual series.
Two series, Trips and Voting Records, span the years 1979-1990 and 1979-1989 respectively. These series catalog the many district visits Leath made and his voting record on Congressional bills. The final series, Audio-Visual, houses photos of Leath with presidents, other Congressional leaders, and constituents during his trips. The second subseries in Audio-Visual comprises radio tapes of his newsletters. Finally, thirty-six oversize boxes containing awards round out the collection.
Arrangement
A preliminary inventory was taken by Leath’s Congressional office in 1990. Material is arranged according to governmental structure and Leath’s office. The series are: I. Administrative, II. Agencies, III. Correspondence, IV. Departments, Boards, and Commissions, V. Executive Branch, VI. Legislative, VII. Press, VIII. Trips, IX. Voting Records, and X. Audio-Visual.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 14. Acquired 1988-09-12
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
Related references
Leath Biography/Obituary. Pace, Eric. "Marvin Leath, 69, Ex-Congressman." New York Times accessed August 16, 2018. [web site]
Leath Congressional Biography. "Leath, James Marvin, (1931-2000)." Biographical Directory of the United States Congress. Accessed August 16, 2018. [web site]
Leath Biography. "Texas Rep. Marvin Leath." Washington Post accessed August 16, 2018. [web site]
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Leath, James Marvin, 1931-2000DLArchives--Indexes.
Subjects (Organizations)
Democratic Party (Tex.); United States. Congress. House--Voting.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Armed Services.; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Department of Agriculture.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of the Treasury.
Places
Texas -- Politics and government.
Subjects
Agricultural laws and legislation -- United States.; Government agencies--United States.; Legislators -- United States -- Archives.; Newsletters.; Politicians -- Texas.; Veterans -- United States.
Genres
Audiocassettes.; Awards.; Business correspondence.; Calendars.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Diplomas.; Directories.; Financial records.; Invitation cards.; Legislative bills.; Legislative materials.; Personal correspondence.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Questionnaires.; Records (Documents); Speeches.; Transcripts.; Yearbooks.
- Administrative, 1975-1990, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Administrative files include a large selection of office and contact files arranged under seven broad categories: 1. General, 2. Calendars and Directories, 3. Groups and Organizations, 4. Invitations, 5. Requests, 6. Schedules, 7. Finances, and 8. Employment. Material included ranges from 1975 to 1990.
  The General subseries includes administrative materials that do not fall into one of the six succeeding categories, including congressional administrative offices, letters of gratitude or condolence, and information regarding district and Washington offices. Interestingly, this also includes information regarding the Poage Library.
  Groups and Organizations comprises two alphabetically arranged sectionsDLone for groups and one for organizations, as distinguished by initial designations given by Leath’s staff. Groups include the Heritage Foundation, the Ku Klux Klan, and the U.S. Olympic Committee; Organizations include the Audubon Society, Veterans of Foreign Wars, and Waco ISD. Typically, groups and organizations are non-governmental in nature, while government entities are arranged in their own series.
  Invitations and Schedules are each arranged chronologically by date.
  Requests demonstrates the broad variety of interests that constituents had in the workings of Congress and the wide variety of favors they requested.
  Finances includes weekly reports and expense vouchers for all of Leath’s Congressional finances, while Employment addresses requests regarding internships at Leath’s Congressional offices. Both subseries are in chronological order.
  - General, 1979-1986, undated; 1
    - A- Files, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A- Files, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Acknowledgements (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Acknowledgements (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Committees, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Airline Information, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Architect of the Capitol, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Attending Physician, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - B- Files, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - B- Files, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - B- Files, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Birthdays and Anniversaries, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Birthday Cards Received, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Botanic Gardens, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - C- Files (1 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - C- Files (2 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - C- Files (3 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - C- Files (4 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - C- Files (5 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - C- Files (6 of 6), 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Capitol Historical Society, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Caterer, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Cards Received, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Gifts Received, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Party List, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Clerk, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Clerk, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Clerk Document Room, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Condolences, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Condolences, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Congratulations, Received (1 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Congratulations, Received (2 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations, Received (3 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations, Sent (1 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Congratulations, Sent (2 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Congratulations, Sent (3 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Births (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Births (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Births, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Births, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Birthdays, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Birthdays, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Birthdays, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Wedding Anniversaries (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Wedding Anniversaries (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Wedding Anniversaries (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Wedding Anniversaries (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Congratulations, Sent, Wedding Anniversaries, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Budget Office, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Club, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Staff Club, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Staff Club, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Contacts, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Coryell Long-Range County Program, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Current Issues (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Current Issues (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Current Issues (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Current Issues, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - D- Files, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - D- Files, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - D- Files, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - District Maps, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - District Office, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - District Office Correspondence (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - District Office Correspondence (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - District Office Supplies, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Document Log Sheets, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Doorkeeper (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Doorkeeper (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Doorkeeper (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Doorkeeper, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Doorkeeper, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - E- Files, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - E- Files, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - E- Files, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - F- Files, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - F- Files, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - F- Files, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Federal Judicial Center, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Federal Parking Fees, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - G- Files, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - G- Files (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - G- Files (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - G- Files (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - G- Files (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - G- Files (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - General Accounting Office, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Goodwill, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Goodwill, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Goodwill, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Government Accounting Office, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Government Printing Office, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Government Printing Office, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - H- Files, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - H- Files, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - H- Files (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - H- Files (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Heart of Texas Community Education Final Report, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hold for Marvin Leath’s Attention, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - House Recording Studios, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - House Restaurant Catering System, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Houston Documentary Expedition, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - I- Files, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - I- Files, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Inauguration Files (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Inauguration Files (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Interns (Lyndon Baines Johnson [LBJ]), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Internships, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - J- Files, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - J- Files, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - J- Files, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Judicial Conference, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - K- Files (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - K- Files (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - K- Files, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - K- Files, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - L- Files, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - L- Files, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - L- Files, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Leath Awards, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Letters (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Letters (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Library of Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Library of Congress, American Folklife Center, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Library of Congress, CRS (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Library of Congress, CRS (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Library of Congress, CRS, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - M- Files, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - M- Files, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - M- Files, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Majority Leader, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Majority Leader, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Majority Whip (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Majority Whip (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Majority Whip, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Majority Whip, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - N- Files, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - N- Files, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - N- Files, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - O- Files, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - O- Files, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - O- Files, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Office, District (Waco), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Office, District (Waco), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Office, District (Waco), Correspondence, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Office, District (Waco), Correspondence, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Office, District (Waco), Supplies, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Office, District (Waco), Weekly Reports (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Office, District (Waco), Weekly Reports (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Office, District (Waco), Weekly Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Office, District (Waco), Weekly Reports, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Clerk, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Doorkeeper, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Legislative Council, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Office of the Postmaster, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Office of the U.S. Court of Appeals, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Office Setup and Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Office, Washington, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Office, Washington, Outgoing Requests, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Office, Washington, Outgoing Requests, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Office, Washington, Office Memos to District Office, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - P- Files, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - P- Files, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - P- Files, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Page Service, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Party Activists in Virginia, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Photographer, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Photographer, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Poage Library, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Police (Capitol Hill), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Publications Distribution Office, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Q- Files, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaires (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaires (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaires, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - R- Files, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - R- Files, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - R- Files, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ratings, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Recommendations, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Recommendations, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Recommendations, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Referrals (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Referrals (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Referrals, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Referrals (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Referrals (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Restaurants, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - S- Files (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - S- Files (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - S- Files, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - S- Files (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - S- Files (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - S- Files (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Sergeant at Arms, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Speaker of the House, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Speaker of the House, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Speaker’s Advisory Committee on Broadcasting, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Speaker’s Rooms, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Superintendent of Buildings, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Superintendent of Buildings, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Supreme Court, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Supreme Court, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - T- Files, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - T- Files, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - T- Files, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Thank-you’s Received, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Thank-you’s Received (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Thank-you’s Received (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Thank-you’s Received, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (1 of 4), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (3 of 4), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (4 of 4), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Thank-you’s Sent (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Turner, Tommy, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Turner, Tommy (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Turner, Tommy (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Turner, Tommy, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - U- Files (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - U- Files (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - V- Files, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - V- Files, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - V- Files, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Visit by Midwood High School, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Visitors (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Visitors (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Visitors, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Visitors (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Visitors (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - W- Files, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - W- Files, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - W- Files, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Waco Transportation Study (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Waco Transportation Study (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Western Union, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Y- Files, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Y- Files, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Y- Files, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Z- Files, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Z- Files, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Z- Files, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Calendars and Directories, 1979-1980; 2
    - Calendar, Historical, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Calendar, Official, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Capitol Directory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Directory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Handbooks, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Congressional Pictorial Directory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - House Telephone Directory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Staff Directory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Staff Journal, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Groups and Organizations, 1977-1983, undated; 3
    - ABC Position Paper, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Accokeek Foundation, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Air Force Sergeants Association, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Alliance of Postal and Federal Workers, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 22)